useiconic.com 2016-03-11

# Privacy Policy

#### Last updated: February 24, 2013

### TL;DR

It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites and the services we provide to you.

  * We use cookies.
  * We _do not_ store your credit card.
  * We will _never_ sell your personal information.

## Our policy

This is the privacy policy for the Iconic website operated by Waybury, LLC. (" **Waybury** ", " **we** ", " **us** " and/or " **our** "). This website was created to provide information about and enable the purchase and download of the Iconic product. This policy applies to all Iconic websites and sub-domains, including, but not limited to, [useiconic.com](http://useiconic.com/) and [blog.useiconic.com](http://blog.useiconic.com/) and sets forth the policy with respect to personally identifiable information and other information that is collected from site visitors.

## Information we collect

When you create an account – to participate in our community forums or during the purchase process, for example – we require an email address (we may send you an email to verify), a first and last name and account password. You may modify any of your information at any time via your account page.

Those who engage in transactions with us – by purchasing Iconic, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with us.

### Information collected automatically

We collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The purpose of collecting this information is to better understand how visitors use our site.

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information, like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, during the purchase process for the purposes of fraud protection and mitigation with our payment processor.

## How we use personal information

We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information, including your email address, to anyone.

We may occasionally send you an email to tell you about Iconic product updates and new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Iconic. We primarily use our [blog](http://blog.useiconic.com/) and website to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.

### Consultants and Third Parties

Like many businesses, we sometimes hire other companies and consultants to perform certain business-related functions. When we use another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

Our community forums service is provided by [Moot](https://moot.it/) and uses their Single Sign-On functionality. If you choose to participate by posting a topic or comment to the forum, as part of the Single Sign-On process we will share your first name, first initial of your last name and email address to support topic update notification functionality you may elect to receive. Moot's privacy policy and terms of service document is available [here](https://moot.it/terms/) for review.

If you have previously created a personal avatar picture with [Gravatar](http://gravatar.com/) that is associated with the email address you share with us, it will be shown to you while you are signed-in and also publicly visible in the community forums while using the forums and along with any posts or comments you create.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact us.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their Site usage, and their Site access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Site, with the drawback that certain features of our websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If Waybury, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the event that Waybury goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Waybury may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. We will notify you before any such transfer event would occur.

## Changes to this policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and at our sole discretion. The latest amended policy will be made available on this page along with a summary history of changes.

#### History

  * February 24, 2014: Initial release

### Acknowledgments

Parts of this Privacy Policy were adapted from the [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) license provided by [Automattic](http://automattic.com/).
